[Music]
hello everyone today I'm going to do a
product review on one of the kids
cameras that I bought from temo for my
daughter and uh this was around $39 New
Zealand doar very cheap compared to
other camera prices and uh this is how
it looks like from the outside and let's
see what uh what's inside and what is
coming along with so this has a user
manual and a charging cable one side is
us and the other side is Type
C and it's coming along with the extra
printing papers two printing
papers and Camera holding
Strand and the
camera so the cool thing is you can
print out the photos at the same time
black and white and for that you have to
insert these printing papers over here
let see how it looks like and that's the
printing paper and before you close drag
a little bit and this black color roller
should go down underneath the paper it's
all done and this has SD card insertion
site uh if you want to save your photos
and videos you can uh use a SD card this
is the Char charging
port and uh that's the switch off
Buton so switch on and off button uh and
then the okay button up and down arrow
keys and the capturing button so let's
let's switch on it
[Music]
first and this is coming along with
several options it has a camera video
recording option music uh for that
actually you have to save music or songs
into the SD card then kids can
hear uh and then uh play back
uh games and settings so let's start
with the first one the camera and see
how it uh capturing images I'm going to
use this
one so you have to press okay go to the
[Music]
camera and press the capturing button
and this is how it get printed out then
you can tear it
apart and that's the quality of the
paper and it's go through some of the
other options to go to back go back to
the main menu uh you have to press the
start
button and
uh arrow keys to go to the other op
options video you can't take videos
because there's no SD card uh in this
camera let's go
back of course
uh music we can't uh I can't show you
because I didn't install a SD
card uh let's go to the
games PR okay and it has four games for
kids
[Music]
and under
settings you can change lot of things
like uh
[Music]
language so English is activated at the
moment and you can change the printing
density it's uh medium at the moment I
change it to
[Music]
high and and then printing
modes so I activated dot print earlier
now we'll change it to gray print and
see how it looks
[Music]
like date and
time and the volume so I want to reduce
the volume
[Music]
then the video
resolution so there are two
[Music]
options camera
resolution I think there are several
options but uh I'm not going to activate
it you can format your SD
card and uh you can set up for power
off after 5 minutes
1 minute and 2
minutes and you can activate the screen
saver after 3
minutes sidey click
record
frequency and default settings you can
go back to always go back to default
settings if you
want so that's all uh about this camera
and let's take another image and see
what differences make it uh after
changing the settings
[Music]
so this is after changing the settings
and that's the one I took
earlier I really don't see much
difference but uh I guess this one is
better compared to the previous one this
one and uh if you want more printing
papers uh you can buy them separately so
this whole 10 piece pack was around five
New Zealand Dollars very cheap and
overall I think this camera is very nice
for kids they enjoy a lot and they can
take photos of different pictures and
they can color them so I'm really happy
with this product